(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Ookami Mio 1st Live. 「Our Sparkle」
Ookami Mio 1st Live: Our Sparkle
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention to all visitors
演出の都合上、照明の明滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Vocal cheering is allowed.
二次販売グッズ
Second Round Merchandise Sales
Ookami Mio 1st Live. 「Our Sparkle」
Ookami Mio 1st Live: 'Our Sparkle'
holoplus 大神ミオジャック！してみた！
holoplus: We let Ookami Mio take over!
2025.9.10 (Wed) PIA ARENA MM
September 10, 2025 (Wed) PIA ARENA MM
Attention / ご来場のお客様へ
Attention / To all visitors
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援 OK です
Cheering loudly is OK.
Ookami Mio 1st Live "Our Sparkle" 二次販売グッズ
Ookami Mio 1st Live "Our Sparkle" 2nd Sales Goods
Sponsor / 協賛
Sponsor
みるハコ by JOYSOUND
Miruhaco by JOYSOUND
あ、こっちこっちこっち！
Ah, over here, here, here!
今日、2人じゃないんすね。
You're not a duo today, are you?
え？2人？
Eh? Two?
さっき、ここで会った人たち。
These are people I just met here.
え？
Eh?
♪ 心で...
♪ In my heart...
ジョイしてこうぜ！
Let's Joy!
JOYSOUND X1
Ookami Mio 1st Live. "Our Sparkle"
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention: To our visitors
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
二次販売グッズ
Second round of merchandise sales
本日は、大神ミオ 1st Live「Our Sparkle」にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for coming to Ookami Mio 1st Live "Our Sparkle" today.
ウチウチ、ウチだよ！ 大神ミオだよー！
Uchiuchi, it's me! It's Ookami Mio!
わー、みんな元気だー！
Wow, everyone's so energetic!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます。
To ensure you enjoy the live show until the end, I have a few announcements.
元気いいね、ふふっ。
You're so energetic, hehe.
公演中の撮影・録音・録画機材の使用は、固くお断りいたします。
The use of photography, recording, or filming equipment during the performance is strictly prohibited.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、無理をせず近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
In the unlikely event that you feel unwell, please do not push yourself and inform the nearby staff.
会場内でのモッシュ・ダイブ、大きく飛び跳ねる、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、
Acts such as mosh pits, diving, jumping excessively, or throwing things onto the stage,
他の皆様の迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
which may cause trouble for others or obstruct the performance, are strictly prohibited.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね！
Please follow the rules and have a great time!
守っていただけない場合は、ご退場いただく可能性もあるので、気をつけてね！
Please be careful, as you may be asked to leave if you do not follow the rules!
また、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、
Also, please note that cameras for video streaming and photography will be in the venue,
客席が映り込む場合がございます。
and the audience seats may be captured.
これらの映像や写真は、プロモーションなどに使用される可能性がございますので、
These videos and photos may be used for promotional purposes,
予めご了承ください。
so please be aware of this in advance.
みんないい子だね！ あははっ。
You're all such good kids! Ahaha.
あ、ライブのハッシュタグはミオスパークルです。
Ah, the hashtag for the live is #MioSparkle.
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてね！
Use the hashtag and get hyped up!
それでは、開演までもう少しです。
Well then, it's just a little bit longer until the show starts.
みんなで一緒に盛り上がってこう！
Let's all get hyped up together!
ミオしゃー！
Mio-sha!
たい　たい　たい　たい
Tai tai tai tai
しゃら　しゃら　ら
Shara shara ra
今日も一日
Today too, all day
がんばるぞ
I'll do my best
もふもふ　ふわふわ
Fluffy fluffy
おなかが鳴るよ
My stomach is growling
にょん　にょん　にょん
Nyon nyon nyon
たい　たい　たい　たい
Tai tai tai tai
しゃら　しゃら　ら
Shara shara ra
今日も一日
Today too, all day
がんばるぞ
I'll do my best
もふもふ　ふわふわ
Fluffy fluffy
おなかが鳴るよ
My stomach is growling
にょん　にょん　にょん
Nyon nyon nyon
ソロライブ楽しもう！！
Let's enjoy the solo live!!
だれが半額じゃい！！！
Who's half-price?!!!
Mio LOADING
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
OUR SPARKLE Ookami Mio 1st Live.
しじまに響いてよ My Howling
Echo through the silence, my howling
大神ミオ1stソロライブ、始まるよー！
Ookami Mio's 1st Solo Live starts now!
ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi!
そっと流れゆく風景 切な的な
The scenery flows softly, sentimental
日々の中で
within the days.
差し伸べられた手は優しく 鼓動に浸る
The hand reached out to me was gentle, soaking into my heartbeat,
微熱の予感
a premonition of a slight fever.
風に攫われる そう生きてきたから
Swept away by the wind, that's how I've lived,
君に会って気づく もう一人じゃない
but meeting you, I realized I'm not alone anymore.
さあ今 瞬きは超え かき消す月へ響く
Now, beyond a blink, echoing to the drowning moon,
つま弾く満ち欠け 今の胸 共に投げく夜
plucking the waxing and waning, this heart, this night we grieve together.
遠く伝播する想いは 心強くさせる
Thoughts propagating afar make me feel reassured.
付いておいでよ 後ろに君がいるから
Follow me, because you are behind me,
私は迷わない
I won't hesitate,
光射す道へ
towards the path where light shines.
無力だから仲間を求め 凍えるから
Because I'm powerless, I seek companions; because I'm freezing,
火を灯して
light a fire.
変化と共に進化してく この顛末は
Evolving along with change, this outcome
誰も知らない
no one knows.
君を信じる そう決めているから
I believe in you, because I've decided to,
どんな非常非情をも 乗り越えられるよ
I can overcome any cruelty or harshness.
げっこう この闇に唯一 凛と咲く花
Moonlight, the only flower blooming gallantly in this darkness.
恐れなのか憧れなのか 向き合う夜空
Is it fear or is it longing? Facing the night sky.
大地を駆け抜ける私と 君が作り出す
As I run across the earth, you and I create
この物語 単純な未来じゃない 湧き立つ情熱
this story, it's not a simple future, but a surging passion.
この声に乗せよう
I'll put it in this voice.
空飛ぶ羽なくても 手を繋げられたから
Even without wings to fly, since we could hold hands,
この運命を選んだ
I chose this destiny.
連想する遠吠えは しじまに響いて
Associated howls echo through the silence,
何度も何度も その絆を確かめ合った
time and again, we confirmed that bond.
瞬きは 声なき月へ響く
Blinkings echo towards the voiceless moon
爪弾く道 金銀の群れ
The road I pluck, a golden and silver flock
共に嘆く夜
The night we grieve together
遠く伝播する思いは 心強くする
Thoughts propagating far away make my heart stronger
共に行こうよ 隣に君がいるから
Let's go together, because you're by my side
私は迷わない
I won't hesitate
光射す道へ
Towards the path where light shines
Listen to my howling
大神が止まることはない
Ookami will never stop
まだまだ走るよー！
We're still going!
みんな、ついてきてー！
Everyone, keep up!
どこまで行こうか ねえ
How far shall we go? Hey
ベイビーな夜空に 映る昨日の自分
In the baby night sky, my yesterday's self is reflected
夢見がちだった ベイビーフェイスにさよなら
Saying goodbye to that dreamy baby face
見たくないもの照らす ハイビームに走る焦燥感
Impatience running in the high beams that illuminate things I don't want to see
跳ね除ければいい 行けば
Just brush it off, and as I go
信号は皆 色を失い消えた
All signals lost their color and vanished
確かめたい 導き繋ぐ先を
I want to make sure of where the guidance leads
深く深く紺になる
Deeper and deeper into navy blue
夜を抜ける この加速度
Passing through the night, this acceleration
光さえ超えていけるほどに
To the point where I can even exceed light
強く強く踏み込んで
Stepping in strongly, strongly
僕は駆ける ただ真っ直ぐに
I run, just straight ahead
譲れない思いを抱いて
Holding onto thoughts I cannot yield
標識だらけの街を 抜け出して
Leaving the city full of signs
明日を探してた
I was searching for tomorrow
常識も何も全部 複雑にしてた
Common sense and everything were making things complicated
どこまで行けるの？なんて
How far can I go?
聞き飽きた台詞 吐いて
Spitting out that phrase I'm tired of hearing
曇った窓ガラスに 書いた本音
The true feelings I wrote on the cloudy window glass
すぐに 指で消した
I immediately erased with my finger
臆病でも揺るぎない 奇跡確かな願いを
Even if I'm a coward, an unwavering miracle, a certain wish
胸に遥か遠く
Deep in my heart, far away
錆び付くように軋んでも この真っ暗を灯し進めれば
Even if it creaks as if rusting, if I light up this darkness and move forward
ただ一つ答えを追いかけて
Chasing just one answer
脆くてもいい この腕で
It's okay to be fragile, with these arms
掴むために 手を伸ばすよ
I'll reach out my hand to grab it
打ち鳴らす鼓動の限り
As long as my heart beats
何度 この道で迷って
How many times have I gotten lost on this road
見失ってどこへ行くの
Losing my way, where am I going?
目指す場所もその意味も 一つしかないのに
Even though there's only one place to aim for and one meaning for it
曇った視界は夜に溶けても もう一度開けていく
Even if the cloudy vision melts into the night, it will open up once more
視線の先 僕を連れて行くよ きっと
Beyond my gaze, it will surely take me there
みんな、行くよー！
Everyone, let's go!
深く深く紺になる
Deeper and deeper into navy blue
息を吸って 今加速度を
Taking a breath, now with acceleration
傷つくほどに強くなろう
Let's become strong enough to get hurt
確かな色 動き出す
A certain color starts to move
まとっているその身体で
With that body you're wearing
鮮やかな夜空の果てへ
Towards the end of the vivid night sky
忘れないように
So I don't forget
深く深く紺になれ 今を生きる この加速度
Become deeper and deeper navy blue, living the now, this acceleration
光だって超えていける場所へ
To a place where I can even exceed light
強く強く踏み込んで
Stepping in strongly, strongly
僕を駆ける ただ真っ直ぐに
I run through myself, just straight ahead
譲れない...
Un-yieldable...
君と思いを抱いて
Embracing thoughts of you
止まらないで
Please don't stop
走り続ける君を知るから
Because I know you continue to run
きっと未来は色に溢れ
I'm sure the future will overflow with colors
まだ見ぬ世界をカラフルに染める
Coloring the world I haven't seen yet
もっと自由になりたいから
Because I want to become even freer
ずっとずっとずっと夢見てるの
I'm always, always, always dreaming
空に光る星のように
Like a star shining in the sky
輝きたいと願う夜
On the nights I wish to shine
広い世界に存在を
To prove my existence
証明したくて
To the vast world
できないことばかり数えても
Even if I only count what I can't do
胸が苦しくなるだけでしょう
It will only make my heart ache, right?
私だって絶対
Even I will surely
あの日の夢のようになれるはず
Be able to become like the dream from that day
響く音色の中ほら
Look, amidst the echoing tones
未知なる景色
An unknown scenery
遠く感じてたのに
Though I felt it was far away
気付いた気がしてたんだ
I felt like I had noticed it
そっと伸ばしたこの手の先
Beyond this hand I gently extended
描いた理想が側を越える
The ideal I drew crosses by me
きっと見つける私の色
I'll surely find my color
ずっとずっとずっと追いかけるの
I'll always, always, always chase it
限りなく透明だった
Everything that was
瞳に映る全て
Infinitely transparent in my eyes
変わり行く世界のリズム
The rhythm of the changing world
モノクロを染めて行く
Dyes the monochrome
閉じ込めなくてもいいの
It's okay not to lock it away
不安感じても
Even if I feel anxious
私だけの色で描こう
Let's paint with only my own color
きっと未来は色に溢れ
I'm sure the future will overflow with colors
まだ見ぬ世界はカラフルに染まる
The world I haven't seen yet will be dyed colorfully
もっと自由に羽ばたくから
Because I will flap my wings even more freely
ずっとあの日感じたままに
Just as I felt on that day
そっと伸ばしたこの手の先
Beyond this hand I gently extended
描いた理想が側を越える
The ideal I drew crosses by me
やっと見つけた私の色
I finally found my color
ずっとずっとずっと描いてくの
I'll always, always, always keep drawing it
ありがとう！
Thank you!
はい！ というわけで
Alright! So,
まずは自己紹介からしたいと思うんですけど
first of all, I'd like to do a self-introduction.
あの... みんなわかってる人とわかってない人いるかもしれないから
Um... since there might be people who know and people who don't,
一応説明するんですが
I'll explain it just in case.
「うちうち、うちだよ！」って言ったら
If I say, "Uchi uchi, uchi da yo!"
みんな「大神ミオだよ！」って言ってもらったら
and everyone says, "Ookami Mio da yo!"
うちの自己紹介が完成するので
my self-introduction will be complete,
言ってもらってもいいですか？
so could you say it for me?
それじゃ、いきましょう！
Then, here we go!
うちうち、うちだよー！
Uchi uchi, uchi da yo!
大神ミオだよー！
Ookami Mio da yo!
わー！
Waa!
本日は大神ミオのソロライブ開催
Congratulations on holding
おめでとうございます！
Ookami Mio's solo live today!
あ、うちがおめでとうって言われる側だと思うんだけど
Ah, I think I'm the one who's supposed to be congratulated,
たぶん
probably.
すごいみんな！
Amazing, everyone!
え、ソロライブの衣装どうかな？
Hey, what do you think of my solo live outfit?
かわいい！ 嬉しい！
"It's cute!" I'm happy!
なんとなんと今回、あの6年と...
Believe it or not, this time, after 6 years...
まあもうちょっとで7年活動してきて
well, almost 7 years of activities,
尻尾が解放されてるんです！
my tail has been liberated!
見て見て！
Look, look!
今までずっと...
Up until now, always...
ここ、あの、足にね、あの、巻き付いていた、
The tail that was, you know, wrapped around my leg...
しっぽがね、見えちゃった感じなんですけれども...
...it's like it's visible now...
ま、これはうちの自信の現れと言いますか、
Well, I guess this is a sign of my confidence, or rather,
自信がついたからこうやってしっぽが開放できたということで。
I've gained enough confidence to release my tail like this.
この舞台に押し上げてくれたみんな、ありがとう！
Everyone who pushed me up to this stage, thank you!
あー、ちょっと、汗かいてきちゃったかも。
Ah, I might have started sweating a bit.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
いやー、ちょっとね、最初だし。
Well, since it's the beginning...
コールアンドレスポンスとか、してみたいけど、どうかな？
I'd like to try some call and response, what do you think?
ちょっとやってみちゃおうかな。さっきね、あの、狼耳にはなってもらったから。
Maybe I'll try it. Since I had you all become wolf ears earlier...
おー、どうしようかな。じゃあ、狼美緒ソロライブって言ったら、
Oh, what should I do... Okay, if I say "Ookami Mio Solo Live",
みんなアワースパークル！って大きい声で言ってもらってもいいですか？
could everyone shout "Our Sparkle!" in a loud voice?
狼美緒ソロライブ！
Ookami Mio Solo Live!
アワースパークル！
Our Sparkle!
ありがとう！すっごいよく聞こえる！
Thank you! I can hear you so clearly!
ちょっとね。配信で見ているそこの君も、
Also, you there watching the stream,
現地席のみんなもよく見えてるよ。
and everyone in the venue, I can see you clearly.
コメントありがとね。
Thank you for the comments.
いっぱい、うちのね、可愛い姿をスクショしてもらえたら
I'd be happy if you could take lots of screenshots
嬉しいなって思います。
of my cute appearance.
現地の皆は一旦記憶にキャプチャーしてね。ありがとう。
Everyone at the venue, capture it in your memories for now. Thank you.
はい、そして。＃ミオスパークルで、
Yes, and please post your screenshots and impressions
スクショや感想のポストもよろしくお願いします。
with the hashtag #MioSparkle.
いやさ、もう、狼美緒ソロライブ。
I mean, with "Ookami Mio Solo Live",
始まっちゃったらもう、あっという間に終わっちゃうのかと思うと、
once it starts, it feels like it'll be over in the blink of an eye.
MCもまだまだ終わりたくないんだけど。
I don't want the MC to end yet.
もう始まった瞬間から終わる心配してるんだけど。
I've been worried about it ending since the moment it started.
はい。今日はね、たくさん最高にキラキラな思い出作っていこうね！
Let's make lots of the most sparkling memories today!
すごーい！
Amazing!
はい、そして。チラ見せ枠の皆さんには残念なお知らせなんですけれども。
Yes, and... I have some sad news for those watching the "sneak peek" portion.
ま、あの、現地の皆さんはね、最後まで見れるのは確定なんですが。
Everyone at the venue will definitely be able to see until the end, but
えー、無料配信は、ここでお別れとなります。
the free stream ends here.
はい。というわけでね、あの、配信のチケット、買っていただければ続きが見れますので。
Yes. So, if you purchase a streaming ticket, you can see the rest.
ぜひぜひ買っていただければなと。ミオファのみんなも思ってるよね？
I'd love it if you could buy one. I'm sure all the Mio-fa feel the same, right?
思ってまーす！
We do!
よろしくお願いします。ミオじーの、皆、出すなよ。
Thank you. Everyone, don't let out your "Mio-ji" persona.
なんか、今、イマジナリーミオファの声が聞こえてくるような...
I feel like I can hear the voices of imaginary Mio-fa...
騒がしいミオファの声ですね。
some noisy Mio-fa voices.
はい。というわけで、そろそろ次の曲、行きますか？
Yes. So, shall we move on to the next song soon?
狼美緒ソロライブ、盛り上がっていくぞ！
Ookami Mio Solo Live, let's get hyped!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!
The free peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
夢を掴み取れ
Grab your dreams
Sparkle!
Our Sparkle!
輝く未来へ 駆け抜けていく
Running towards a shining future
君と笑い合えたなら それだけでいいんだ
If I could laugh with you, that would be enough
いつまでもずっと 響け このメロディ
May this melody ring out forever and ever
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.